and who are you mobile Zro contract soldier Who are
а ты кто мобили Зро контрактник Кто
you I am a bream
ты Я лещ
who am I a mite I am a mercenary and I thought a
кто я клещ я наёмник а я думал
mite My name is Irakli you are
клещ Меня зовут Ираклий вас
like Alexey I am from the city of Kuta
как Алексей Я из города Кута
where I know the city myself
откуда города сама
My father served in Samara when he was still in the Soviet Union
знаю у меня отец когда в Советском Союзе
in the
Самаре это вы где-то в
hospital No, I’m the one who just rented
госпитале Нет я это я сейчас снял
a room to have a
комнату для того чтобы
drink. I mean, you rented a room, you don’t
попить В смысле снял комнату это вы не
live
живёте в
in Samara. No, I live in Samara, that is.
Самаре Нет я живу в Самаре то есть
Now I’m in the project to buy an apartment, that
Сейчас в проекте покупать квартиру то
is. Well, for now. Well,
есть Ну пока что Ну
we’re looking for Tosi Bosi. But I don’t want to go to my sister’s.  to
как Ищем тоси боси А у сестры не хочу
be drunk I heard There mortgages have now
пьяным быть я слышал Там ипотека сейчас
raised the
подняли
conditions even more How will you now buy
ещё условия ещё сильнее Как вы купите
an apartment for cash
квартиру за наличные
Yes, that is, I’m a former
Да ну то есть я я-то бывший
miner A former crane operator
Шахтёр бывший крановщик
earned normal money in my time I understood
нормально зарабатывал в своё время понял
Listen, how do people in Russia
Слушайте а как вот у вас в России люди
feel about the fact that  Russia attacked
относятся к тому что Россия напала на
Ukraine
Украину
calmly, the sanctions imposed
спокойно на вас же санкции наложили
so many problems on you, so much money you
столько проблем столько денег у вас
spend on this war. Why do you need it? Well,
уходит на эту войну Зачем оно вам Ну
look, for example, I
смотрите для того чтобы вот я допустим м
work,
работаю
I work as a crane operator, my salary is
я крановщиком работаю у меня зарплата
approximately 90-100,000, despite the fact that I
приблизительно 90-100 000 при том что я
don’t  I’m going to the Tower, well, I’m too lazy to
не не иду на Башенный ну мне лень на
climb the Tower. I’m going to the Mostovoy to climb the
Башенный лезть Я иду на Мостовой на
gantry crane. Maybe you know such a
козловой кран Может ты знаешь такую
profession as a crane operator, I know, I know. My
профессию крановщик знаю знаю У меня
grandmother was
бабушка была
a crane operator, so I don’t climb that to the top.
крановщик вот я не лезу на это на верха
Damn, now now maybe the connection will
Блин сейчас сейчас возможно связь
be lost a little
чуть-чуть пропадёт
so that  no damn,
вот для того чтобы не блин
living purely on
прожить чисто на
groceries is enough for my ears,
продукты мне за уши хватает
about
приблизительно
30,000 purely on
30.000 чисто на
groceries, that is, I don’t limit myself in anything,
продукты то есть я себе ни в чём не
well, alcohol is a market No, that’s a
ограничиваю ну алкоголь базар Нет это
plus
плюс
Well, 10-15, roughly speaking Well, let’s be
Ну 10-15 сся грубо говоря Ну будем
honest with
честными правильно
ourselves, that’s right, and now I
собой вот ну и вот вот
understand A  you had a lot of acquaintances taken away by the
понял А у тебя Знакомых забрало много на
war, well, there are a lot of acquaintances in the war
войну ну на войне много
[music] there are
[музыка]
a lot of acquaintances and there are already those who died,
много а уже есть такие которые погибли
how many
есть сколько
died Yes, we don’t know enough of the whole
погибло Да достаточно мы не знаем всей
Truth Well,
Правды Ну
although you know how many acquaintances died there is
хотя ты знакомых знаешь сколько погибло
no need for the truth not the truth You know, there
не надо правды не правда Ты знаешь вот
was Vanka and  Vanka is gone
был Ванька и нету
and
Ваньки и
that’s it Well, you’re fighting. I’m in Georgia in general.
всё Ну а ты воюешь Я в Грузии вообще
Well, I actually asked, well, you have a
Ну я вообще спрашивал ну у тебя плак
Ukrainian banner, I’m from Georgia, I’m watching. I
украинский я с Грузии смотрю Я тебя
asked you why you attacked Ukraine and
спросил зачем вы напали на Украину и
How many of your friends
Сколько твоих знакомых
died Yes, it’s normal that she died Well, damn
погибло Да нормально погибла Ну блин
direct
прямых
friends,
знакомых
since they’re so direct about  com I’m a little bit sorry
раз таких прямых о ком чуть-чуть сожалею
[music]
[музыка]
Yeah, six is
Угу шесть
a cool good number,
прикольно хорошее число
no, I’ll
что нет я тебя
make you happy, considering that
обрадую при том что
I’m the deputy
я зам командира
squad commander, you’re just the deputy
отделения ты прям зам командира
squad commander, I
отделения я
understand. I think there’s
понял Я думаю
no such thing, yes, leave for injury, now
такой нет да отпуски по ранению сейчас
show the wound, you say that you’re
покажи рану ты же говоришь что ты
a crane operator. Well  it’s
крановщик Ну по
really cool to be wounded And this is that
ранению прикольно реально А это что
the bullet flew right through Yes no Tanchik
прилетела пуля насквозь Да нет Танчик
Tanchik this is fragmentation
Танчик это осколочная
it’s made of
это
flint, it
кременное
turns out to be some kind of American The tank
получается какой-то американский Танчик
fired and like you were scattered there yes Well,
стрельнул и типа вас рассыпала там да Ну
what kind of
какой
these are there like in or what are the old
там этих как в или какие там старые
Soviet ones Listen, it turns out that this is a
советские Слушай а получается такой
question like also interesting  is it from your
вопрос типа тоже интерес это из твоего
platoon that died, or like
взвода погиб или как
one friend and five are from the
один друг и пятеро это с
squad And how many people in the squad are
отделения А сколько в отделении
six, wait, out of six, five
человек шесть подожди из шести пятеро
died, you were the only one left
погибло ты остался один
alive
живой
Yes, it’s a rotten, rotten, rotten feeling Well, you can
поганое поганое ощущение Ну ты можешь
restore justice, you
это восстановить справедливость тоже же
can too Well, like, the boys should go on a visit
можно Ну типа пацанам пойти типа в гости
Like a solidary Damn, well, you’re in Ukraine,
Типа чтоб солидар Блин ну ты на Украине
I think so, you’re fighting this too Yes, I don’t
я так думаю ты тоже это воюешь Да я не
know, I’m in Georgia I’m telling you, my
знаю я в Грузии Я же тебе говорю меня
name is Irakli I’m from the city of Kutaisi Yes, you
зовут Иракли Я из города Кутаиси Да флаг
have the Ukrainian flag. Geolocation of Ukraine
Украины стоит у тебя геолокация Украины
And I turned on the geolocation VPN, I
А геолокацию я включал VPN я с
communicated with Ukrainians  before that, I didn’t change
украинцами общался до этого я не поменял
to Russia, yes, I talked and asked how
на Россию да я общался спрашивал как у
they were doing. Well, well, I’m calm, I’ll
них Ну вот ну Я спокойно отношусь я
let you have a second now, and who are you, mobile,
допустим сейчас секунду а ты кто мобили
Zro contract, who are
Зро контрактний кто
you, I’m the sharpest,
ты я хлеще
who am I, the sharpest? I’m a mercenary And I thought
кто я хлеще Я наёмник А я думал
a tick I say, I’m a bream Wagner
клещ Я говорю я лещ Вагнер
Dana and  was there too and was there too Well,
Дане и там тоже был и тоже там был Ну а
when was the injury This is what department were you in?
когда вот ранение Это в каком ты
Hired in this in the Ministry of
наёмного в это в Министерстве
Defense And how much do they
обороны И сколько
pay? Yes, they pay normally, don’t
платят Да нормально платят вообще не
worry about money, but before the war What did you work for
парь о деньгах а до войны Кем работал до
before you started killing people for
того как пошёл убивать людей за
money before that?  how I went to work I went to
деньги до того как пошёл работать пошёл
work as a crane operator so
работал крановщиком так
crane operator salary approx. I
крановщик зарплата приблизительно Я тебе
told you you didn’t listen I heard I just
говорил ты не слушал я слышал Просто я
thought you were kidding salary my
думал что ты прикалывался зарплата моя
salary 100 This is for the lazy, that is, the
зарплата 100 Это для ленивого то есть
minimum wage for the lazy
минималка для ленивого
80 that’s how much in the war sko
80 вот а сколько на войне ско
pla
пла
and in the war a mercenary how much do you get
а на войне наёмник тебе сколько
they pay 250 they pay me
платят 250 мне платят
That is, you went for the money,
То есть ты за бабки пошл
yes
да да Зачем мне бабки Я и так нормально
yes, why do
зарабатывал Не ну ты
I need the money? I was already making good money. No, you didn’t refuse money for the money.
же ты не отказался за бабки
Well, why
пра Ну а почему бы
not? I have a wife, we have children, we
нет Жена дети есть мы
work, of course we have everything, I understand, and in
работаем есть конечно всё есть понял А в
what city is the wife?  kids,
каком городе жена дети
how are you and how are you? Are you a
вот а у тебя как А у тебя как дела Ты
blogger? To be honest, I’m not a blogger. I’m
что блогер Если честно не не блогер Я я
from Georgia. I just came out to talk. I’m
из Грузии Я просто вышел пообщаться Мне
interested in the conflict between Russia and Ukraine.
интересно про конфликт России и Украины
I went out and talked to the Ukrainians. Now I’ve
Я вышел с украинцами пообщался сейчас
turned it on with the Russians.
включил с россиянами общаюсь мне
I’m wondering
мне Мне интересно
how I got such an attitude, damn it’s an enemy in front of me
как я такого отношения блин передо мной
and you were still in prison,
враг и всё в тюрьме ты сидел
no. How did you even end up
нет А как ты вообще попал
nano And how did you end up as a
нано А как ты попал
mercenary? Well, you went on your own and that’s it. Well, like,
наёмником Ну сам пошёл и всё Ну как типа
here you were. You were sitting there, your wife, should you
вот ты был Сидел сидел там жена тебе
sleep, or were you walking along?  on the street I saw a
спать или ты шёл по улице увидел
recruiting point like No, I
рекрутинговый пункт как Нет я так
thought so to myself My country is at war And that
подумал что себе Моя страна воюет А что
I’m sitting and that’s all And in what year did you go
я сижу и всё А в каком году ты пошл
in the twenty-second and second And when in
в двадцать втором д втором А когда в
what
каком
month Damn at the end of the year in
месяце Блин в конце года в
December I honestly say in December I understood,
декабре честно говорю в декабре понял
well,  that Mit with the
вот ну а что Мить
soul,
душой
but it turns out well,
вот а хорошо получается
look at why you kill people in
смотри ради чего ты убиваешь людей в
Ukraine
Украине
Let’s look at it differently I
Давай по-другому нужно смотреть Я
work and it’s not okay, wait, there’s a job, there’s a drug
работаю и всё не ну подожди работа есть
courier, he also works, but he
наркокурьер он тоже работает но он
sells drugs, you kill people for
разводит наркотики ты убиваешь людей за
money Yes, that’s also work, it
деньги Да это тоже работаешь
turns out to be a courier He  slowly killing it
получается курье Он медленно убивает это
with drugs No, why did you go to work as
наркотиками Не ну зачем ты пошл работать
a killer of
убийцей
Ukrainians? Listen, let’s say I’m going on an
украинцев Слушай я вот допустим иду на
assault, think opposite me,
штурм думай напротив меня
you’re shooting at
ты ты стреляешь в
me. Agree, I’m asking you why did you
меня Согласись я тебя спрашиваю зачем ты
even become a mercenary to be
вообще пошёл наёмником чтобы тебя
sent to the
отправили На
assault? I just told you once
штурм я я тебе только что сказал как-то
my country is at war and
моя страна воюет А
I am fighting for what is she fighting for what is she for her
я воюет за что она воюет за что она за
homeland for her homeland but she is not fighting in her
Родину за Родину но воюет не в своей
homeland but somewhere in someone else’s homeland Listen listen
Родине А где-то в чужой Родине Слушай
Listen well look now here
слушай Слушай ну смотри вот сейчас у вас
in Georgia
в Грузии
some moments are happening how you support them  or
некоторые как ты их поддерживаешь или
not, tell me about Ukraine, tell me about
нет мне про Украину расскажи ты мне про
Ukraine Tell me I just don’t care Well,
Украину Расскажи Я просто негу по Ну вот
answer me please I am
ты мне ответь пожалуйста Я
against me in the elections I will vote
против я на выборах Буду голосовать
against this
против этой
government No, those who say
власти Не ну которые говорят
this are like his gender reassignment clinics in
это как его клиники по смене пола в
Georgia this is very terrible here  Look,
Грузии это это очень ужасно у нас Смотри
I wanted to change the
я хотел сменить как раз в
floor just last month, but I didn’t have time because
прошлом месяц пол но не успел потому что
we had such queues, we said
у нас такие очереди были мы что сказали
that they would ban it, they banned IR, unfortunately, I
что запретят запретили ИК сожалению да
’ll have to now Well, I’ll stay without changing the floor
придётся теперь Ну не менять пол
As it is Well, well, it turns out That’s
останусь Как есть Ну ну получается Это
what you mean with this with the old
самое ты значит с этим со старым
laminate  you will Well yes for now I will yes
ламинатом будешь Ну да пока буду да
I’m telling you about
я тебе говорю про
something else look and now you tell me
другое смотри а теперь ты мне расскажи
That’s why you went Your country went to
Вот зачем вот ты пошл Твоя страна пошла
kill people in Ukraine what does it want
убивать людей в Украине что она хочет
why did it come to
зачем она пришла в
Ukraine a buffer zone and that’s all I mean a
Украину буферная зона и всё В смысле
buffer zone You just lived people  in
буферная зона Вот вы просто жили люди в
Ukraine they just
Украине просто
lived when when Ukraine wanted to
жили когда когда Украина захотела
join NATO, that is, to
вступить НАТО то есть
drag it into Ukraine and
затащить уже к себе на Украину и
bring it closer to our borders, then this is
приблизить это к нашим границам то это
no longer not Ukraine, this is already NATO nuclear
уже не не Украина это уже НАТО ядерное
weapons So what? Well, what do we have to
оружие Так и что Ну а что нам нужно
do? live as we
делать жить как
lived Yeah and  and okay, let’s release this
жили Ага и и ладно отпустили бы этот
option
вариант
now Now And in 5-10 years we
сейчас Сейчас А через 5-10 лет нас бы
simply wouldn’t exist
просто не стало
so you’re gone now, look Ukraine is
так вас сейчас не стот смотри Украина
already taking out all your warehouses Yes, in the
уже выносит ваши склады все Да вон в
Tver region I’m begging you Begging Come on
Тверской области умоляю Умоляй Давай
Begging the Kursk region
Умоляй курскую область
already Damn it’s a circus Well, like a circus  The Republic of Kazakhstan just
уже Да блин это цирк Ну как цирк РК как
fled, in
убежал
short, and
короче а в Грузию
ours to Georgia. Why did you attack Georgia in 2008?
наш Почему вы в 2008 году на Грузию
Well, how did you want to go
Ну а как Вы захотели заходили
where they went,
кудава заходили
Dakhin - this is our Georgian city Well, well,
дахин - это наш грузинский город Да ну
under your nose, the rest of the armed forces are ours again
ваши под носом остальное ВС наше ещ раз
Well, like Khiva - this is the territory of Georgia, this is
Ну как Хива - это территория Грузии это
not
не
Russia in the end In the end, everything is fine
Россия в итоге В итоге вал всё нормально
now, without you,
живёт сейчас без вас
Khiva is pinned down by the brothers and live as they want
Хива прижат братья и живут как хотят
Dagestan Dagestan you are one of the Dagestani
Дагестан Дагестан ты из дагестанцев
boys You know I know I know they say
пацанов Знаешь Знаю знаю они говорят
Russian So [ __ ] it Yes And I was a
русских Так что капец да А меня
Dagestani
дагестанец
Chechen in the
чеченец по
hospital treated like this, it’s cool
больничке лечили вот так вот прикольно
because it’s necessary  E send so
потому что тея надо Е отправить чтоб
that you
че те е
still need to work. Of course, that’s what I’m
ть ещё поработать нужно Конечно этоже я
saying, like you should make it out of you, I have
же говорю типа ты должен из тебя выжит у
friends around me with different
меня вокруг друзья разные
functionality, I’m me, in general, so that
функциональность я это я вообще чтобы
it’s like that, for
это так чтобы так для
peace of mind, I won’t show the token number. I
успокоения номер жетона не буду
don’t see my
показывать Вот мой позывной не вижу
call sign here.  something that is not ours is
позывной тут что-то не нашему написано
not written in Georgian How can you read it I don’t
не по-грузински Как можешь прочитать не
know there is something there in both Russian and English
знаю там и по-русски и по-английски там
Uzun I don’t know what this
что-то Узун такое Я не знаю что это за
word is Well Uzun is my call sign And what is
слово Ну Узун мой позывной А что такое
Uzun
Узун
long this is familiar translation with
длинный это знакоми перевод с
Turkic Turkic Are you a
тюр тюркский А ты что
Tyurik? I lived in Kazakhstan for many years.
тюрик я много лет прожил в
I have a kilometer of friends of different
Казахстане У меня друзей километр разных
nationalities. And if Kazakhstan
национальностей понял А если Казахстан
wants to join NATO, you will go to fight
захочет вступить в НАТО пойдёшь воевать
against
против
Kazakhstan. Kazakhstan will not want to join
Казахстана Казахстан не захочет вступить
NATO, but if it wants, the Americans
в НАТО а если захочет вот американцы под
say, Well then, that’s it
говорят Ну тогда это
then. In short, I understood  okay, good luck,
тогда Короче я понял ладно давай удачи
look, you're just a demagogue, come on, let's
Вот вот ты просто демагог поди Давай
talk after all, well, you're afraid
давай поговорим всё-таки Ну ты боишься
just because I'm thee at the fact, I have a
просто потому что я тея при фак У меня
friend just calling Yes, my friend keeps calling me, come
друг просто звонит Да мне друг звонит
on Be two hundred, come on, Glory to
всё давай Будьте двухсот ты Давай Слава
Ukraine, come
Украине Да ну
on, these are the ones who
давай вот
are going to kill  people in Ukraine for
такие и идут убивать людей в Украине за
money for money he goes my country couldn’t
деньги за бабки он идёт страна моя не
sit of course damn 2 times
мог сидеть конечно блин в 2 с по раза
more than a crane operator once and went that’s
больше чем крановщиком раз и пошёл вот и
all subscribe to my Telegram right
всё подпишись на мий Telegram прямо
away the axis of wine and
зараз ось вин а
popk more and more respectfully YouTube Zaga
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube Зага
us through skarg  op in your ban and a
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
lot more video I don’t show people at the moment don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about the stream For this
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
purpose, we need to write a Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
right away and in the meantime, in Telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video shchezh Tsikava and Korisna
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we blame you Trima
информация и мы повинни вами трима
postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
regardless  in this chi show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine write
YouTube Слава украини пиши